menprovement.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Menprovement

## Privacy Policy

**MENprovement Privacy Policy**  
The following privacy statement covers all of MENprovement websites. Please read this statement regarding our websites. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Ownership of Information**  
MENprovement is the sole owner of the information collected on the MENprovement websites.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the MENprovement websites, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. MENprovement does not endorse these comments as they are opinions of users not associated with MENprovement or it’s employees.

**Mailing List**  
MENprovement may launch a mailing list for some or all of the MENprovement websites. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, MENprovement has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by MENprovement only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on MENprovement websites are delivered to users by third party advertisers including Google, among others. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) This site allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information, when you and other Internet users visit. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information,  
browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this site and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. Users may opt out of behavioral targeting through the opt-out link [HERE](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, MENprovement may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the MENprovement websites.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event MENprovement goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**  
MENprovement contains links to other sites. Please be aware that MENprovement is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by MEnprovement.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever MENprovement changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

**Copyright Information**  
All images on MENprovement.com are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)  
If you believe that any content appearing on MENprovement.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know. E-Mail menprovement[at]gmail[dot]com  
following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.  
(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf  
Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.
